[auto]Sitting on the mountain and sea
[auto]Fudi is worthy of its name
[auto]Fuzhou, as the provincial capital of Fujian, this paradise
[auto]Nature is a blessed place like a name
[auto]Strolling in Fuzhou
[auto]Eat meat yan
[auto]keep us safe
[auto]The mountains on the back contain peculiar mountain treasures
[auto]The long coastline brings a dazzling array of seafood
[auto]Backing by the mountains, eating the mountains, by the sea, eating the sea
[auto]Fuzhou people combine the two skillfully
[auto]A table of Fujian dishes with mountain and sea flavors
[auto]Fuzhou eats too much
[auto]In the mountains and in the sea
[auto]Flying in the sky and crawling on the ground
[auto]Both have
[auto]go
[auto]Take you to Fuzhou to enjoy the blessing
[auto]Wow, it's delicious
[auto]Special offer five yuan
[auto]The most lively food in a city
[auto]Often not at the banquet
[auto]Just look at the lights of the food stalls
[auto]Even a hungry belly
[auto]Can quiet down instantly
[auto]Come, have a drink
[auto]Don't stop drunk
[auto]Bring a bottle of red wine
[auto]Give away
[auto]boss
[auto]Business is booming
[auto]thanks
[auto]My name is Zheng En
[auto]Nicknamed Hu Yidao
[auto]I used to have an uncle
[auto]He is a cook
[auto]I admire him
[auto]But what does this have to do with you?
[auto]What does it have to do with me
[auto]I started working as a chef when I was seventeen
[auto]Became a chef at the age of twenty-three
[auto]Participating in a food competition
[auto]I won the first place as a knife worker
[auto]The brilliance of the knife
[auto]Prove Hu Yidao's orthodox background
[auto]And as a Fujianese chef
[auto]Drunk Crab is doing well
[auto]It's also a matter of fame
[auto]Fuzhou people grew up eating seafood
[auto]Deal with their pickiness
[auto]Not to be sloppy
[auto]Go to four or five markets to choose crabs every day
[auto]It's Hu Yidao's daily life
[auto]Boss lady
[auto]This fifteen yuan
[auto]That’s what it means to be very tall and weak
[auto]One is round and the other is triangular
[auto]With a little black
[auto]The back is also fuller
[auto]It feels that its feet are tight
[auto]This kind is the best
[auto]All right
[auto]Gills and hairy eggs need to be removed
[auto]Must use live
[auto]Dead can't eat
[auto]Not a word
[auto]Often good ingredients
[auto]Only the easiest way to cook
[auto]Fresh live crab
[auto]Wash and cut into small pieces
[auto]Sterilize with 52-degree white wine to remove fishy and improve freshness
[auto]The taste of crab is more delicious and fragrant
[auto]Seaweed
[auto]soy sauce
[auto]Mustard
[auto]Chili rice
[auto]Raw shrimp
[auto]Celery cut into small pieces
[auto]Then pour sweet, vinegar and sesame oil
[auto]Plus a little mustard
[auto]and many more
[auto]Why is the blended juice only half used?
[auto]It turns out that after marinating and refrigerating
[auto]Pour out the previous juice
[auto]Add new juice
[auto]It is said that this can get rid of the fishy smell of the crab
[auto]delicious
[auto]Don't think this is all
[auto]There is also an important support
[auto]This is jellyfish skin
[auto]Jellyfish produced this year
[auto]Whole piece large
[auto]Soak
[auto]Q bombs are delicious
[auto]Jellyfish crispy
[auto]Drunk Crab is Fresh and Soft
[auto]Convergence of different textures
[auto]Let this joint performance be harmonious and brilliant
[auto]smell
[auto]The smell of the sea
[auto]Umami
[auto]Then this is fresh
[auto]Authentic taste
[auto]Sweet and sour
[auto]Must order this sister loves it
[auto]It's very delicious
[auto]Come every day
[auto]To queue
[auto]No. 20
[auto]The regional characteristics of Fujian cuisine ingredients are very distinctive
[auto]Know how to cook
[auto]Unique ingredients that have never been heard in other places
[auto]Authentic Fujian Cuisine Chef
[auto]Must know it well
[auto]Cordyceps sinensis
[auto]Limb
[auto]Mobs, also known as grass insects
[auto]More common in Fujian and Guangdong
[auto]In the year
[auto]The days when you can eat fresh scorpions
[auto]No more than a week
[auto]Cleansed stream
[auto]Slowly fry in a frying pan
[auto]You can smell its unique scent
[auto]Stir fry with chives
[auto]Garnish with onion and sesame oil
[auto]The aroma is more diffused
[auto]Can't stop the entrance
[auto]Very comfortable to eat
[auto]It's cool to eat in the mouth
[auto]Good body
[auto]Come
[auto]Fire up
[auto]The fire must be flourishing
[auto]Wanghuo raises the heat
[auto]It will be crispy when fried like this
[auto]Hu Yidao spent more than 30 years
[auto]Temper yourself into a qualified Fujian cuisine chef
[auto]This pride
[auto]Make him look casual
[auto]Inside, he sticks to the rules of cooking
[auto]Cook your own dishes
[auto]You look back
[auto]You are dissatisfied
[auto]If you are not satisfied with what you have done
[auto]How to share with guests
[auto]While reading
[auto]my wish
[auto]Be a chef
[auto]that time
[auto]Do it yourself slowly, think about it
[auto]After so many years
[auto]My wish has come true
[auto]The guests ate very happily
[auto]I feel very happy
[auto]I have this shop at least three times a week
[auto]Put this taste
[auto]Flow in and put it in my stomach
[auto]Put it in my heart
[auto]My friend across the street, i love you too
[auto]One-third of the sky is doomed
[auto]Seven points by hard work
[auto]Love to fight to win
[auto]Everyone cheers
[auto]cheers
[auto]The colors of Fuzhou
[auto]Voice of Fuzhou
[auto]Every bit of Fuzhou
[auto]We will all remember
[auto]Supper is refreshing
[auto]Breakfast is peace of mind
[auto]Fuzhou breakfast on the table
[auto]It is also a fusion of mountains and seas
[auto]Wok Edge Laohua Meat Yan Fish Ball
[auto]Fullness is not a problem
[auto]The taste is more smooth
[auto]Eat this big brother by the pot
[auto]Is breakfast so early for Fuzhou people?
[auto]4:30 in the morning
[auto]Have eaten for more than ten years
[auto]Come here to eat so early every day
[auto]Come around four o'clock
[auto]I'll be here at three o'clock
[auto]Eighty-something
[auto]Eighty-five
[auto]A bowl of pancakes every day
[auto]A bottle of strong wine
[auto]This is the original old snack in Fuzhou
[auto]Pan side triangle cake oil cake
[auto]Especially you see many old comrades eat here
[auto]Fujianese living away from home
[auto]As soon as I heard the word "gubian"
[auto]A deep homesickness almost immediately
[auto]It also proves that this kind of food
[auto]Iconic status in Fuzhou
[auto]Sister Zhang, Fuzhou Guobianji desperately Sanniang
[auto]Five yuan has been paid
[auto]Eleven yuan has been paid
[auto]Nine yuan has been paid
[auto]Seven yuan has been paid
[auto]Looks mediocre
[auto]But it’s the breakfast C bit on the streets and alleys
[auto]But Sister Zhang’s family is still uniquely favored by diners
[auto]If you grind it twice, grind it twice
[auto]It's tender
[auto]It tastes different when you eat it
[auto]Can only be used
[auto]Sister Zhang, the simplest vegetarian material
[auto]Would rather be every day
[auto]One hour less sleep
[auto]Also have the best taste
[auto]Packed ten bowls
[auto]A few bowls short
[auto]This one is hot and this one is warm
[auto]Hot
[auto]Shrimp into the pot to make the soup base
[auto]Use oiled kohlrabi
[auto]Brush around the edge of the pot
[auto]Then pour the ground rice syrup on the side of the pot
[auto]The experienced foodie glanced at the side of the pot
[auto]I know the master’s practice is enough
[auto]Must be an even circle
[auto]A little more and a little less are not good enough
[auto]Sprinkle the seaweed and chopped green onion at the end
[auto]This ordinary food with a mountain and sea flavor
[auto]Was born
[auto]The golden partner on the side of the pot is oil cake
[auto]I have eaten for almost 20 years
[auto]Toothless old
[auto](Can only) eat slowly
[auto]The dried shrimp is very delicious when paired with this seaweed
[auto]I am a native of Fuzhou
[auto]Since childhood
[auto]Grandparents will
[auto]Get up early in the morning and take me there
[auto]Pot side stall
[auto]I love her, she is not from Fuzhou
[auto]I also think she can
[auto]Experience the local breakfast in Fuzhou
[auto]The baby came out after that
[auto]I will also bring them to eat
[auto]Eat authentic Fuzhou breakfast
[auto]In the old days, the side of the pot was where people were in the fields
[auto]Eating while working
[auto]With another pancake
[auto]Warm confidant
[auto]This allows Fuzhou people to remember its taste
[auto]time to eat
[auto]Four yuan has been received
[auto]The boss is out of soup
[auto]one more bowl
[auto]Until now
[auto]The side of the pot at Sister Zhang’s house has never changed
[auto]The soup can be refilled for free
[auto]All you can eat
[auto]What are you eating for four yuan a bowl
[auto]Have done it for decades
[auto]In the morning fireworks of this city
[auto]A pot warms all kinds of diners
[auto]Also mixed into the lives of many Fuzhou people
[auto]Become in the taste of life
[auto]Indispensable blindness
[auto]Fujian cuisine ranks among the eight major cuisines in China
[auto]Many of them are exquisite
[auto]Fuzhou cuisine this branch
[auto]Especially emphasize light refreshing
[auto]Good at fresh soup
[auto]The first Buddha jumped over the wall
[auto]But the people of Fuzhou
[auto]It’s not that every meal can be eaten so much
[auto]In ordinary and lively days
[auto]What's on their table
[auto]Didn't you read the wrong time?
[auto]This noon
[auto]I'm close to the meal
[auto]Why are you so leisurely?
[auto]This is the boss, Brother Hua
[auto]These two old ladies
[auto]Are the boss’s mother and mother-in-law
[auto]This is the lady boss Hong
[auto]The old man who is practicing calligraphy is the father of the proprietress
[auto]The grandfather drinking tea is the boss’s father
[auto]Hello
[auto]Still the third
[auto]good
[auto]I will arrange now
[auto]start work
[auto]Put more shrimp oil
[auto]I got it ok
[auto]Hello
[auto]Twenty minutes, right?
[auto]Ok ok
[auto]and many more
[auto]Why does the boss call so many calls?
[auto]Are all regular customers
[auto]They are all guests of our community
[auto]I'll be down after ten minutes after making a call
[auto]Very convenient
[auto]Lychee meat, right
[auto]I'll make it for you right away
[auto]okay bye
[auto]Lychee meat is a sweet and sour taste
[auto]Sister Hong will join specially
[auto]Half-ripe tomatoes for seasoning
[auto]Will make the taste more sour, sweet and refreshing
[auto]The ingredients for this dish are not complicated
[auto]But the knives are the most important
[auto]Use fresh pork tenderloin
[auto]Cross Sword Flower
[auto]Just wait for the pot
[auto]Let oil and fire help transform
[auto]Sprinkle in cooking wine
[auto]Marinate for 20 minutes
[auto]Then hot oil
[auto]Pour in the marinated meat
[auto]Flip fry
[auto]Curl the meat into a lychee shape and remove it
[auto]Fry the prepared potato wedges
[auto]Sweet and sour tomato sauce, etc.
[auto]Tune into sauce
[auto]Put the tenderloin potatoes into the pan and stir fry
[auto]Guarantee every piece of tenderloin and potatoes
[auto]Can be evenly wrapped
[auto]This sweet and sour sauce
[auto]He did the same as lychee
[auto]Sweet and sour
[auto]Here comes the lychee meat
[auto]Your favorite baby
[auto]The sweet and sour must be just right
[auto]Bibimbap is really delicious
[auto]The lychee has a (pattern) on it
[auto]It has to cross-cut flowers
[auto]Need to use a flower knife
[auto]He said well, he is also a chef
[auto]We all call him Uncle Chen
[auto]I came over for dinner before the lady boss got married
[auto]We have opened a store for more than ten or twenty years
[auto]I often come over to eat if I don’t like cooking at home
[auto]They all say that Fujian cuisine has a deep doorway and it is difficult to cultivate
[auto]A community shop
[auto]Can actually get
[auto]The recognition of so many Fuzhou gluttons
[auto]Boss lady
[auto]Are you secretly hiding any tricks?
[auto]No
[auto]Because our street is called Yangnan Street
[auto]The name of our restaurant is Yangnan Hotel
[auto]I was born and raised in this community
[auto]80% of our customers here
[auto]All from our community
[auto]Because they often come (to eat)
[auto]I naturally remembered their habits
[auto]Don't need to be too sweet
[auto]too sour
[auto]Can't drink
[auto]Then I will cook some corn whiskers
[auto]Make some herbal tea
[auto]For these guests to drink
[auto]One community, hundreds of flavors
[auto]Maybe there are only some subtle differences
[auto]But for diners who patronize all year round
[auto]Enjoy more than the taste
[auto]It's also the sense of exclusiveness that I'm thinking about
[auto]Look at this table full of food
[auto]The name of the dish alone can make the saliva secrete automatically
[auto]Lychee Pork Drunk Pork Ribs Stir-fried Double Crisp
[auto]Red lees meat, red lees small intestine, red lees fish, light lees eel
[auto]slow!
[auto]I heard that this dish is a bit advanced
[auto]In Fujian cuisine
[auto]This is also a challenge to test your skills
[auto]Generally small restaurants rarely have this dish
[auto]Time-consuming to deboning eel meat
[auto]It takes more than 20 minutes for a dish
[auto]The meat from the middle section of the fresh conger eel
[auto]Cut into approximately two finger widths
[auto]Red lees, ginger shreds, cooking wine
[auto]Shrimp oil
[auto]Shrimp oil must be talked about
[auto]Oops shrimp sauce
[auto]If you don’t know how to eat shrimp oil, you’re not a Fuzhou native
[auto]So amazing?
[auto]Open this tank to show you
[auto]In order to ensure the authenticity of the eel
[auto]The choice of shrimp oil is crucial
[auto]Sister Hong’s designated workshop
[auto]Have been doing it for more than fifty years
[auto]This oil is good
[auto]Shrimp oil commonly known as fish sauce
[auto]During the Guangxu period of the Qing Dynasty
[auto]There have been some small workshops in Fuzhou
[auto]They put the fish and shrimp in the jar
[auto]Sun and night dew stirs morning and evening
[auto]Marinated for months, shrimp oil was born
[auto]Seasoning mixed with shrimp oil
[auto]Make a spa for the conger eel
[auto]The modulation ratio relies on Sister Hong’s years of experience
[auto]One hour long
[auto]It can make the eel have a light wine aroma
[auto]It can also make the color bright red attractive
[auto]Heavy makeup, so beautiful
[auto]Finally, deep fry over medium heat until cooked
[auto]Out of the pot
[auto]Tick ​​clean
[auto]Wrap evenly and deep-fried crisply
[auto]Every step is required
[auto]Focus
[auto]I ate a few bowls of rice that day
[auto]Three bowls
[auto]I need to prepare more rice today
[auto]We have been eating here for a long time
[auto]Her mother from
[auto]Before my daughter was married
[auto]Eat here
[auto]Now her daughter is so old
[auto]right
[auto]Watching her get married and have children
[auto]very beautiful
[auto]There are 30 to 40% of such regular customers
[auto]From middle age to more than seventies
[auto]Some are from children
[auto]To get married and have children
[auto]They have also witnessed the growth of our shop
[auto]We have also witnessed the changes in their lives
[auto]Treat it as a home
[auto]I can talk in short days
[auto]Understand their situation
[auto]When i'm here
[auto]He will understand my situation
[auto]So I just didn't know it
[auto]Want to treat him as a relative
[auto]thank you all
[auto]In many rapidly changing cities
[auto]Have familiar neighborhoods
[auto]Already considered a blessing
[auto]The authentic taste that has been passed down for generations
[auto]Still in the same place
[auto]Fuzhou people who have grown up for generations
[auto]Inherit the shared taste memory
[auto]Still come to eat
[auto]Come
[auto]How old is it to eat
[auto]Eighty years old
[auto]Used to be the annual sales champion
[auto]Earn more than three million a year
[auto]Three cars
[auto]This kind of car is a toy for adults
[auto]Hey, Long brother
[auto]How come your adult toys look like this
[auto]It's still nothing to wash the dishes
[auto]Sometimes I have to wash the toilet
[auto]Have to do everything
[auto]Choi Sum will make up immediately
[auto]Lian Long, the former toy brother
[auto]Now the one who knows comes to the helm
[auto]In fact, they are all very detailed
[auto]Some trivial things
[auto]But you have to do it seriously
[auto]Sea oysters and bone marrow are mandatory
[auto]And fish roe
[auto]Fried fish roe
[auto]Lady preparing to cook
[auto]It's the boss's wife Lin Lin
[auto]Stir-fried noodles and white mushrooms should be quick
[auto]How to drink the Arctic Ocean
[auto]Arctic Ocean blow off
[auto]Blow off
[auto]This shop was founded by my father-in-law
[auto]Me and my wife
[auto]Had to take over this shop
[auto]Dirty, bitter and tired
[auto]Very disgusted
[auto]quick
[auto]Guisan has a copy
[auto]Four
[auto]I will cook fish roe
[auto]Serve
[auto]Speaking of letting the knower come
[auto]The secret of a real smile
[auto]In the hearts of all heroes
[auto]All have an answer that coincides with each other
[auto]Quack stunt
[auto]Bone marrow pot
[auto]Tell the truth about this thing
[auto]The only store in Fuzhou has
[auto]Inside the hotel
[auto]It's impossible to make this bowl of food for you
[auto]He has a special taste of Fuzhou here
[auto]I can only describe it as indelible
[auto]A bone marrow pot that has been walking the rivers and lakes for many years
[auto]Naturally, there are many particulars
[auto]Pour bone marrow into water
[auto]Boil slowly
[auto]Take out the bone marrow in about half an hour
[auto]Put pork bone marrow, shiitake mushrooms, wolfberry secret ingredients
[auto]Put it in the bone soup
[auto]Simmer
[auto]Two to three hours
[auto]It not only guarantees the Q bomb of bone marrow
[auto]Increased the sweetness of the soup bone soup
[auto]When my father just opened the shop
[auto]Many taxi drivers eat in the store
[auto]Then they reported that their waist hurts
[auto]Because they drive for a long time
[auto]My father thinks this formula of bone marrow and old wine
[auto]Can help them with calcium
[auto]They think it has this effect
[auto]Then my father kept doing it
[auto]Mrs. Lin Lin told me
[auto]Since 1996
[auto]Father Lin Shiqing founded till now
[auto]There is a rich variety of pots from the know
[auto]Mountain delicacies and seafood take turns
[auto]Clay pot, mussel pot, three belly pot, etc.
[auto]Everything
[auto]Fuzhou people really play nourishment to the extreme
[auto]Our clay pot
[auto]The last fresh and titian
[auto]Rely on this
[auto]The finishing touch in the pot
[auto]It's the secret sesame oil left by Linlin's father
[auto]Five pounds of pork suet
[auto]Three pounds of shallots
[auto]Three pounds of garlic
[auto]If this doesn't work well
[auto]If its taste is not pure
[auto]If it smells a little bit burnt
[auto]The whole claypot has no soul
[auto]Fresh shrimp oil
[auto]In addition to the smell of old wine
[auto]Sesame oil enhances fragrance
[auto]The perfect bowl of bone marrow pot is complete
[auto]Smooth
[auto]The taste of Fuzhou
[auto]Old taste
[auto]Tastes old
[auto]There is this bone marrow soup
[auto]I'm afraid of drinking with you
[auto]Here, the wine is poured
[auto]continue
[auto]Come again
[auto]Where is the sea oyster
[auto]Install a copy for me first
[auto]Sea oyster bone marrow
[auto]Oyster
[auto]In Fuzhou, which is rich in seafood
[auto]Oysters are a must-have dish in every restaurant
[auto]The simplest processing
[auto]Fight is fresh
[auto]Sister Hong
[auto]Hello
[auto]In order for diners to eat the freshest sea oysters
[auto]Eight in the morning
[auto]The couple began to prepare
[auto]It's all good
[auto]Then take 50 catties today
[auto]Fresh sea oysters salvaged that day
[auto]Get rid of fine sand and impurities
[auto]Boil water for five minutes
[auto]It happens to be the most tender time
[auto]Fresh
[auto]Wow
[auto]Fatter than me
[auto]This kind of dish does not require much cooking
[auto]Is solid materials
[auto]Smell of the sea
[auto]Dip with shrimp oil is enough
[auto]good to eat
[auto]I’m not feeling well recently, I need to make up
[auto]I think we are not only regular customers
[auto]We are still old friends
[auto]It's all Brother Bang (Lin Shiqing) watching us grow up
[auto]Then we watched you grow up
[auto]Actually not only the boss and the customer
[auto]More brothers and confidants
[auto]Dad always wants us to come back
[auto]Also talked for many years
[auto]But we have been looking down on
[auto]After the end of 2013
[auto]There is an emergency
[auto]The old man at home is gone
[auto]Then had to take over
[auto]Met some old customers
[auto]Who he said you are
[auto]Then i said
[auto]This is my father
[auto]He said to do well
[auto]From their
[auto]It can be seen in the eyes of old customers
[auto]Their feelings for this store
[auto]This shop is for him (father)
[auto]Second child
[auto]He loves me very much
[auto]nice to me
[auto]From the sales champion of the year
[auto]Reluctant to take over a restaurant suddenly
[auto]To today
[auto]Has forged an inseparable bond with the shop
[auto]The couple walked all the way
[auto]Just known
[auto]I always wanted to protect
[auto]actually
[auto]It's father's taste
[auto]I hope (diners) they can still think of my father-in-law
[auto]Or it can
[auto]Think of something from the knower
[auto]This shop can give them
[auto]Have some good memories
[auto]Go slowly
[auto]Bye-Bye
[auto]Three minutes is doomed, seven minutes depends on hard work
[auto]This is the spirit of Fujianese
[auto]Strolling in Fuzhou
[auto]This is the faith of Fuzhou people
[auto]It's good here
[auto]Very good here
[auto]Sweet and sour
[auto]Is the characteristic of a table of Fujian dishes
[auto]Never see you all day long
[auto]So early in the morning
[auto]Sister Zhang is still the same
[auto]Visit the park with parents every night as usual
[auto]Talk about trivia at home
[auto]Busy taking care of the stomachs of the people in the community every day
[auto]Hua Ge and Hong Sister
[auto]Choose to sneak in from the busy
[auto]Let yourself relax
[auto]It's you
[auto]I dreamed of you
[auto]On the twenty-fifth anniversary of the founding of Zhizhelai
[auto]Lian Long and Lin Lin
[auto]Celebrate with the employees
[auto]It's better to add a little mustard
[auto]That's right
[auto]As for the Hu Yidao who indulged in cooking
[auto]And started with his chef friends again
[auto]Discuss new dishes
[auto]Blowing the sea breeze
[auto]Looking at Fukuyama
[auto]As a food director who lives at home
[auto]I was in Fuzhou
[auto]I gave birth to a few thoughts of homesickness
[auto]Jianghu Restaurant
[auto]See you next time